<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Quality Assurance on HungerRush Handheld Documentation</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/quality-assurance/</link><description>Recent content in Quality Assurance on HungerRush Handheld Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 12:03:51 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/quality-assurance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Objectives</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/quality-assurance/objectives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/quality-assurance/objectives/</guid><description>OBJECTIVES QA will identify and report defects, ensure the product is error-free, check it conforms to client specifications, evaluate visual components and highlight UI/UX issues by adopting the mindset of the end user.
Primary QA objectives shall include but are not limited to:
Unpacking business requirements during planning sessions Creating QA related test plans and onboarding documentation Design and execute test cases Plan and create test runs Identify issues and troubleshooting Track and report defects Make suggestions to enhance the user experience Attend product related meetings Refine and optimise workflows Report to product owners and / or business stakeholders</description></item><item><title>Testing Methodology</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/quality-assurance/testing-methodology/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/quality-assurance/testing-methodology/</guid><description>TESTING METHODOLOGY A mixture of automation and manual testing will be conducted ensuring products conform to business requirements, designs and behave as expected.
Unit Testing
We are using NUnit for Unit Testing.
First level of testing to be scripted and conducted by developers Ensure individual units of code work as intended / designed at code level Integration Testing
Ensure individual components work as intended Framed by user scenario stories Automated tests by developers / manually tested by QA End-to-End Testing</description></item><item><title>Testing Phases</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/quality-assurance/testing-phases/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/quality-assurance/testing-phases/</guid><description>TESTING PHASES Analysis QA (and stakeholders) analyse past, present and future user stories Identify testable requirements Extract Acceptance Criteria and compare against project Roadmap Create tests to cover all positive / negative scenarios and edge cases Strategy NEW FEATURE TESTING
Occurs once all the tasks of a story are completed by developers When QA team has capacity to validate the ticket Tested on multiple devices, operating systems and browsers (where possible / necessary) REGRESSION TESTING</description></item><item><title>Test Case Development</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/quality-assurance/test-case-development/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/quality-assurance/test-case-development/</guid><description>TEST CASE DEVELOPMENT QA will create test scenarios that can be run against different user types, products / services, environments, devices etc.
Test cases should provide sufficient detail to cover acceptance criteria and include the following for each scenario:
TITLE relating to the story, sub-task or action LINKED to a correlating story or sub-task PRIORITISED correctly with P0-P3 rating EVIDENCED correctly with ticket comment, visual aids etc… ESTIMATED run time added after execution LABELLED correctly REVIEW</description></item><item><title>Defect handling</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/quality-assurance/defect-handling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/quality-assurance/defect-handling/</guid><description>DEFECT HANDLING When an issue is observed the QA team should:
Make sure the issue is reproducible Get another team member to verify Raise necessary bug ticket and share with the team Bug prioritisation should follow the below rating system, which takes into account how severely the bug impacts the system and how urgently it should be fixed / eradicated from the site. If necessary QA should consult a developer or PO to make sure the correct priority is given.</description></item></channel></rss>