<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Domain on HungerRush Handheld Documentation</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/</link><description>Recent content in Domain on HungerRush Handheld Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 16:09:34 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>API resources</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/systems/api-resources/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 16:05:49 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/systems/api-resources/</guid><description>General Architecture There is a Windows VM which has been deployed which acts as a resource to run the POS API. On this VM we are able to start the POS test server
which the client uses to send and receive data from.
HungerRush Handheld Infrastructure This repository represents the IaC for the HungerRush Handheld project and is built and maintained in Terraform. You can also login into Azure portal using the iciuser@devrevention.</description></item><item><title>CI CD Process</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/systems/ci-cd-process/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 16:05:49 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/systems/ci-cd-process/</guid><description>Continuous Integration &amp;amp; Continuous Delivery Continuous Integration and automated testing is done through a combination of writing unit tests for the development language used for the project and Azure Devops.
Azure workflow steps are created on Azure Devops and the yaml config file is maintained on there Developers write unit tests Code changes are committed to GitHub Developers create a pull request on GitHub Azure pipelines are triggered for changes on the development branch If any tests fail the code should not be merged into another branch The apk that is build and signed on the container on Azure Devops is distributed to the app center</description></item><item><title>POS Setup</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/systems/pos/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 16:05:49 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/systems/pos/</guid><description>HARDWARE Prerequisites Make sure you have the right POS device. Hera51 If POS device isn&amp;rsquo;t available, an Android phone is fine for testing. Operating System Ensure the device runs Android Nougat (version 7.1.0 or higher)
Platform Repositories Hungerrush-handheld-order-and-pay This represents the POS app. We’ve followed a an MMVM approach in the implementation of this app.
Setup git clone git@github.com:IIIMPACT/hungerrush-handheld-order-and-pay.git Documentation Setup The documentation is built using GitHub pages, Hugo and the Hugo-Learn template.</description></item><item><title>Payments</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/domain/payments/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 14:34:06 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/domain/payments/</guid><description>Payments refers to a secondary bounded context involving payment mechanisms. Currently, these are common to both customers and consumers. This will likely be refined when this work is planned out further.
Docket The term &amp;ldquo;Docket&amp;rdquo; refers to all information relating to an open table or a consumer order, that is relevant to the consumer themselves. A docket does not include information that is only relevant to the kitchen,
A docket typically includes information such as:</description></item><item><title>Test Server Setup</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/systems/server/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 16:05:59 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/systems/server/</guid><description>HungerRush Server (SandBox environment) Prerequisites On a windows server machine, make sure you have these installed. Microsoft SQL Server 2019 or higher Microsoft SQL Server Management Studio Visual Studio .NET Framework 4.5 Database files iiimpact users can access this link Powershell or Windows Terminal. On a Mac computer, make use of Parallels virtual machine and install the above. Key Repos Make request to HungerRush to provide access to these repos on Azure Devops.</description></item><item><title>Identity</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/domain/identity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 14:36:57 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/domain/identity/</guid><description>The bounded context of Identity is the source of truth for user authentication and properties.
Customer The term &amp;ldquo;Customer&amp;rdquo; refers to a restaurant owner.
Consumer The term &amp;ldquo;Consumer&amp;rdquo; refers to a person who is purchasing food.</description></item><item><title>Hungerrush</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/language-reference/hungerrush/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 15:56:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/language-reference/hungerrush/</guid><description>This document describes terms used internally at HungerRush which do not necessarily match terminology that we use. This is because we have tried to use language which makes sense in the context of each domain, or matches industry standard language.
Site The term &amp;ldquo;Site&amp;rdquo; refers to a single restaurant chain managed by a Customer. As a Customer, I can manage multiple restaurant chains under a single account.
A site is analogous to a merchant.</description></item></channel></rss>