<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Processes on HungerRush Handheld Documentation</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/</link><description>Recent content in Processes on HungerRush Handheld Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 17:53:31 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Development Processes</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/development-flow/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 18:10:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/development-flow/</guid><description>Git We follow a gitflow like strategy. All changes are made in branches based off of master Branches are merged into master via PR Frontend applications are deployed to individual sandbox environments for each pull request. Frontend applications are automatically deployed to staging when merging to main Backend applications are deployed to a dedicated staging environment when being merged to master Backend applications are deployed to production when invoking the release workflow We use strict semantic versioning on all packages.</description></item><item><title>Definition of Ready/Done</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/definition-of-ready-done/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 18:11:15 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/definition-of-ready-done/</guid><description>At each stage of a task or story&amp;rsquo;s progression we have a set of criteria that must be met before the task or story can be moved to the next stage. This is known as the Definition of Ready (DoR) and Definition of Done (DoD).
Selected for development (DoR) We have designs We have assets Are there integration points available Do we have API keys Do we have API documentation Are the requirements clear Do we have Acceptance Criteria Development (DoD) PR is open and well detailed It satisfies all the Acceptance Criteria (AC) It passes all the checks (tests, coverage, linting, etc.</description></item><item><title>File structure Guide</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/file-structure-guide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 18:11:15 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/file-structure-guide/</guid><description>File Structure To easily edit this table use the following link tablesgenerator and copy the markdown table into the editor.
Type Description Location Example View User Interface Views/&amp;lt;Context&amp;gt;/&amp;lt;Name&amp;gt; Views/Auth/LoginView.xaml Model Business Objects that encapsulate data and behavior of application domain Models/&amp;lt;Context&amp;gt;/&amp;lt;Name&amp;gt; Models/Employee/EmployeeMail.cs Data Access Model Data transfer object for passing on values, ends in Obj Models/&amp;lt;Context&amp;gt;/&amp;lt;Name&amp;gt; Models/Employee/EmployeeObj.cs ViewModel Link between Model and View OR It Retrieves data from Model and exposes it to the View ViewModels/&amp;lt;Context&amp;gt;/&amp;lt;Name&amp;gt; ViewModels/Auth/LoginViewModel.</description></item><item><title>Testing</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/test-coverage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 18:11:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/test-coverage/</guid><description>At IIIMPACT, we require that all work has a unit test coverage of at least 70%. This is a minimum however, all code should be covered to a level which considers all critical and functional components.
Your project should stipulate the test tech stack and the minimum coverage required.</description></item></channel></rss>