<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ADRs on HungerRush Handheld Documentation</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/adrs/</link><description>Recent content in ADRs on HungerRush Handheld Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 12:05:51 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/adrs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Architecture Design</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/adrs/architecturedesign/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 17:05:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/adrs/architecturedesign/</guid><description>Status proposed Context We need to layout and document the layout of our codebase. Miro Decision Documenting the layout of our codebase. Documenting Models, Views &amp;amp; View Models as well as functionality and responsibilities.</description></item><item><title>Code Styles</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/adrs/code-styles/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 17:05:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/adrs/code-styles/</guid><description>Status proposed Context We need a structed set of rules to define how we go about code styling/formating Decision Using Sonar Cloud in our CI &amp;amp; Local Linting process to enforce code styles in the HandHeld Codebase Using ReSharper/Rider for local linting and formating Consequences Formatting and linting will be enforced in the CI process using Sonar linting for detecting coding issues in real-time and get clear guidance on how to fix them.</description></item><item><title>Code Patterns</title><link>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/adrs/code-principles/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 17:05:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://iiimpact.github.io/hungerrush_handheld_docs/engineering/processes/adrs/code-principles/</guid><description>Status (proposed) Context We need a structured set of rules to define how we go about code patterns, such as how we handle exceptions, logging, etc. We need to define a set of patterns that we can use to ensure consistency across the codebase Decision Using MVVM as our base pattern for all UI code Using SOLID/DRY/KISS/YAGANI Design Principles as our base patterns Consequences Code will be more readable and structured.</description></item></channel></rss>